-Who doesn't love Anne Hathaway? Thank you for coming.
谁不喜欢 Anne Hathaway 呢？谢谢你来到这里。
-That's very nice. But you know when you have a moment, you're just like, "Oh, I'm gonna remember that forever." Thank you so much for that.
这真的太好了。但你知道，当某些瞬间发生时，你会忍不住想："哦，我会永远记住这一刻。"真的非常感谢。
-There you go. It just happened. Come on. The Roots.
看吧，就是这样，它刚刚发生了。来吧，The Roots。
-Thank you for playing "Reverse Charades" with me. You're a great partner.
谢谢你和我一起玩"反向猜词游戏"。你是一个很棒的搭档。
-I mean, are you competitive when you play games? Do you play games at home?
我的意思是，你玩游戏的时候会有竞争意识吗？你在家会玩游戏吗？
-Oh, I don't mean to be.
哦，我不是故意想这样的。
-I know. Me neither.
我知道，我也是。
-I don't mean to be. But then you saw her over there, I was like, "No, it's just a nice, friendly game."
我本来不是这样的。但后来我看到她在那里，我就想："不，这只是一个友好的游戏。"
-And then the last, I'm like, "But the points are on. Like, it's on."
但到了最后，我就变成："可是现在开始算分了，认真起来了。"
-Let's go. I want to win this.
来吧，我想赢。
-Something takes over. I'm less competitive now.
好像有什么东西控制了我。不过现在我没那么好胜了。
-I think maybe being competitive is genetic, because my kids are, like – They're competitive, too.
我觉得也许竞争意识是遗传的，因为我的孩子也是这样——他们也很有竞争意识。
-And it turns out motherhood has softened me, and I like to watch them win.
结果发现，成为母亲让我变得柔软了，我喜欢看着他们获胜。
-My kids are very competitive, too. Well, my one daughter is. Yeah. Yeah. The other one doesn't really care.
我的孩子也很有竞争意识。不过，我其中一个女儿是这样。另一个其实不太在乎。
-She's like, "That's fun. It's all good."
她会说："挺好玩的，没关系。"
-But the other one really wants to win.
但另一个真的很想赢。
-And I don't throw the games. You know, I go – I really – And I play for – I play for money, too.
而且我不会故意输掉比赛。我是真的认真玩——而且我还会赌钱玩。
-Are you – Is there a party game that you're especially good at?
有没有什么聚会游戏是你特别擅长的？
-No. I mean, you know, I was playing a game – We play a lot of Pokémon and we play a lot of Trouble and Sorry!
没有。我是说，我们会玩很多 Pokémon，也会玩 Trouble 和 Sorry 这些游戏。
-But there is a game – I was working last week and I was on set, and we were just passing the time.
不过有一个游戏——上周我工作的时候在片场，我们只是用它来打发时间。
-And have you seen that movie trivia game where it's cards and they just asks you questions?
你见过那种电影知识问答游戏吗？就是卡片形式，然后它会问你问题。
-And I was just having one of those, like, runs where I couldn't miss.
那天我刚好进入了一种状态，就是怎么都不会答错。
-Like, I just knew and I was, like, surprising myself.
就是我好像都知道答案，甚至连自己都觉得惊讶。
-Well, you know your stuff. You know movies.
毕竟你很懂这些东西，你懂电影。
-I didn't – I mean, apparently, I do.
我以前并不觉得——不过看来我确实懂。
-And then I got to this one question, and they were like, "Oh, okay. So, uh, junior executive assistant, 'Devil Wears Prada.'"
然后我遇到一道题，他们说："好的，问题是：《穿 Prada 的女王》里的初级行政助理。"
-I'm just like, "Emily Blunt." And they were like, "No." And it wasn't her. It was me.
我马上说："Emily Blunt。"他们说："不对。"结果不是她，是我。
-Do you ever – Do you kind of do a project and then you kind of block it out of your mind or no?
你有没有这种情况——完成一个项目之后，会把它暂时从脑海里抹去，或者不再想它？
-You just – It just so happens you…
还是说你只是……恰好会……
-I don't know. I'm not huge on looking back.
我不知道。我其实不太喜欢回顾过去。
-It is kind of funny when – Like, because, you know, I was in this movie when I was 17 years old called "The Princess Diaries."
这其实挺有趣的，因为你知道，我 17 岁的时候出演了一部电影，叫《公主日记》。
-I watch you all the time. To this day, I watch you all the time.
我一直看你的作品。直到今天，我仍然经常看。
-It must be your girls.
一定是你的女儿们喜欢吧。
-We love you. Yeah, they love you so much.
我们都喜欢你。是的，她们真的非常喜欢你。
-I love that it's become kind of one of those family touchstones.
我很喜欢它变成了那种家庭共同记忆中的重要作品。
-So, anyway, people quote it to me all the time, and I don't know what they're talking about.
所以，不管怎样，人们总是引用里面的台词跟我说，但我甚至不知道他们在说什么。
-I haven't seen it in a minute.
我已经有一阵子没看了。
-But "Devil Wears Prada" – I recently saw a photo of you and Anna Wintour.
不过说到《穿 Prada 的女王》——我最近看到了一张你和 Anna Wintour 的照片。
-You made your kind of Broadway debut together in "Gutenberg! The Musical!"
你们还一起在《Gutenberg! The Musical!》中完成了某种意义上的百老汇首秀。
-Did the crowd go nuts?
现场观众是不是疯狂了？
-So, they – So, by the way, I have to say, that's Josh Gad and that's Andrew Rannells.
所以，他们——顺便说一句，我必须说明，那是 Josh Gad，那是 Andrew Rannells。
-They're both dear friends.
他们都是我非常亲密的朋友。
-And they're so – They were so brilliant in the show. It was really next level.
他们真的非常出色。他们在那个节目里的表现简直达到了新的高度。
-And at the end of the show, they invite two people up onstage.
节目结束时，他们会邀请两个人上台。
-And, so, they said my name first, and the audience had a very nice reaction.
于是他们先念了我的名字，观众反应非常友好。
-And then they said Anna's name, and it was like rock star.
然后他们说到 Anna 的名字，现场反应就像见到了摇滚明星一样。
-Because you don't really see Anna do many things that are outside of her –
因为你其实很少看到 Anna 做那些超出她平时形象范围之外的事情。
-Wear a trucker hat.
比如戴卡车司机帽。
-Yes, exactly. You'd never see Anna Wintour, from Vogue, wear a trucker hat.
对，完全正确。你永远不会看到 Vogue 的 Anna Wintour 戴卡车司机帽。
-But everyone just went nuts. She's also a New York icon.
但所有人都疯狂了。而且她也是纽约的标志性人物。
-She's a worldwide icon.
她是全球性的偶像。
-She's everything.
她简直代表了一切。
-Is she fun to share the stage with?
和她一起登台是不是很有趣？
-Yeah. Yeah, really, really fun. And just – She's been incredibly sweet to me.
是的，非常有趣。而且她一直对我特别好。
-And I'm very – I'm just very grateful for our relationship.
我真的非常感激我们之间的关系。
-Do you get nervous around – I get a little nervous –
你在她身边会紧张吗？我会有一点紧张。
-I absolutely do.
当然会。
-You do? Now, I have less to lose, because I'm never going to be on the cover of Vogue, so I have nothing to worry about.
你会吗？不过我压力小一点，因为我永远不会登上 Vogue 封面，所以我没什么可担心的。
-But she likes me, and we've been friends for a long time, so I kind of – I'm comfy around her.
但她喜欢我，而且我们已经做朋友很久了，所以我在她身边还挺自在的。
-I try to keep it comfy. I try to keep it cozy.
我尽量让氛围保持轻松自在。
-But inside, my heart is – I just respect her so much.
但内心深处，我其实非常尊敬她。
-I got the respect and also the dig at the same time. So it was perfect.
我同时感受到了你的尊敬，也感受到了你的调侃，所以非常完美。
-That's how well I know you. That's how cozy I am.
这就是我有多了解你，这就是我们有多自在。
-I saw you, and it was at the…
我看过你的表演，那是在……
-"Twelfth Night" at the Delacorte Theater.
是在 Delacorte Theater 上演的《第十二夜》。
-You were amazing. Do you get nervous? Does anything go wrong? Nothing went wrong when I saw you.
你真的很棒。你会紧张吗？演出中会出现什么问题吗？我看你演出的那次没有任何问题。
-Nothing went wrong? Thank goodness.
没有出问题？谢天谢地。
-Well, because – So, the Delacorte Theater is an outdoor theater in Central Park.
因为——Delacorte Theater 是位于中央公园里的一个露天剧场。
-And so – And you're doing Shakespeare.
而且你演的是莎士比亚戏剧。
-And it rained almost every night.
而且几乎每天晚上都会下雨。
-And so, but it's kind of amazing, because every night, the last line of the show, which we actually sang, was "for the rain, it raineth every day."
但这其实很奇妙，因为每天晚上演出的最后一句台词——我们实际上是唱出来的——是："因为雨水，每一天都会降临。"
-And so the audience, at that moment, always burst out laughing.
所以，每到那个时候，观众总是会突然爆笑。
-And the whole show was so joyful.
整个演出都充满了快乐的氛围。
-I had such a wonderful time.
我度过了一段非常美好的时光。
-But one night, something – I don't know if it went wrong, but something happened.
但有一天晚上，我不知道这算不算出错，但确实发生了一些事情。
-And so, there's this scene. My character, Viola – she comes onto the stage.
有这样一个场景。我的角色 Viola 登上舞台。
-And I knew that the line was funny, but I couldn't figure out how to make it funny.
我知道这句台词本身很好笑，但我不知道怎样才能把它演得好笑。
-So every night, I was just trying something, just anything I could think of.
所以每天晚上，我都会尝试一些东西，任何我能想到的方法。
-And I was, you know, go out there, audience wouldn't laugh, and I was like, "Tomorrow."
然后我就上台，观众没有笑，我就想着："明天再试。"
-And then, one night, I went out there and I said the line, and just the house went down.
然后某一天晚上，我上台说出了那句台词，整个剧场都沸腾了。
-You killed it.
你太棒了。你表现炸裂。
-Killed. And I was like, "Oh, I found it. This is such a good feeling."
真的成功了。我当时想："哦，我找到感觉了。这感觉太棒了。"
-And so then, of course, I leaned into it, because you do.
所以后来，当然，我顺势加强了这种感觉，因为演员都会这么做。
-And so I lean into it and I'm just – The audience is losing their minds.
于是我继续投入进去，而观众简直疯狂了。
-I look under the wings, the cast is losing their minds.
我看向舞台侧边，演员们也都激动疯了。
-I'm high-fiving myself in my head.
我在心里和自己击掌庆祝。
-I'm just like, "I've arrived. This is happening."
我当时想："我终于达到这个境界了，这真的发生了。"
-And I get offstage and I'm just like, "Well…"
然后我下台之后，我就想："嗯……"
-And they go, "Did you see the raccoons?"
然后他们说："你看到那些浣熊了吗？"
-And I'm like, "The…what?"
我说："什么……？"
-And then they just go, "Behind you. As soon as you came onstage, a family of raccoons came out."
然后他们说："就在你后面。你一上台，一家浣熊就出来了。"
-They were so cute. Couldn't focus on the scene because the raccoons were so cute.
它们太可爱了，大家都无法集中注意力，因为浣熊实在太可爱了。
-So I was like, "Well, actually, high five to the raccoons."
所以我就想："好吧，其实应该给浣熊击个掌。"
-See? You got to work with everybody.
看吧，你必须和所有人合作。
-You play well with others.
你很擅长和别人合作。
-Let's talk about "The Idea of You." Oh, my gosh, buddy.
我们聊聊《The Idea of You》吧。天啊，朋友。
-The trailer alone has gotten over 125 million views.
光是预告片就获得了超过 1.25 亿次观看。
-It crushed, broke the record.
它取得巨大成功，打破了纪录。
-Most-watched trailer of any streaming movie in history.
这是历史上所有流媒体电影中观看次数最高的预告片。
-Can we set up what the movie's about?
我们可以先介绍一下这部电影讲什么吗？
-The story is about Solène Marchand, who is a woman who lives in Silver Lake.
这个故事讲的是 Solène Marchand，她是一位住在 Silver Lake 的女性。
-She's a gallery owner. She's a mom and she's got this really wonderful life.
她是一名画廊老板，也是一位母亲，她拥有非常美好的生活。
-And she unexpectedly meets the lead singer of the biggest boy band in the world, a 24-year-old young man named Hayes Campbell.
然后她意外遇到了世界上最大男团的主唱，一个名叫 Hayes Campbell 的 24 岁年轻人。
-And he thinks she's kind of great.
而他觉得她非常不错。
-And so the story is about how they fall in love.
所以故事讲述的是他们如何相爱的过程。
-Because you're just a mom and you're chaperoning this thing and you go to this thing and then you see this boy band.
因为你的身份只是一个母亲，你负责陪同参加这个活动，然后在那里遇到了这个男团。
-I love hearing you describe my movie.
我喜欢听你描述我的电影。
-"Just a mom in this thing." "
只是一个妈妈而已。"
-So, my daughter is off watching St. Vincent.
所以，我女儿去看 St. Vincent 的演出了。
-Because she doesn't like the boy band anymore.
因为她已经不喜欢那个男团了。
-She liked them in seventh grade.
她七年级的时候喜欢他们。
-But, anyway, I have a backstage pass, so I'm an all-access thing.
不过，不管怎样，我有后台通行证，所以我是可以进入所有区域的人。
-I have to go to the bathroom. Somebody tells me where the trailers are.
我需要去洗手间，有人告诉我演员休息车在哪里。
-I go and I walk into the wrong trailer.
我走过去，然后进入了错误的休息车。
-And the rest is – High jinks ensues.
然后接下来就发生了一连串有趣的事情。
-But remind me of the actor who plays the lead singer.
不过提醒一下我，那个饰演主唱的演员是谁？
-Nick Galitzine. -Oh, man, you guys have great chemistry.
天啊，你们两个的化学反应太好了。
-Did you know when he was auditioning? You go, "Oh, this the guy."
他试镜的时候，你是不是马上就觉得："哦，就是他。"
-Oh, yeah. Yeah, no, as soon as he – I actually burst out laughing when he walked in.
哦，是的。他一走进来的时候，我实际上直接笑了出来。
-Because – Has anybody here read the book?
因为——这里有人读过这本书吗？
-No, we don't read. -Well, you should. It's fabulous.
-没有，我们不读书。  -你们应该读。它非常精彩。
-This is "The Tonight Show." Yeah, you want to go over to Stephen Colbert if you want to get people that read books.
这里是《The Tonight Show》。如果你想找读书的人，你应该去 Stephen Colbert 那边。
-We don't read. Lame!
我们不读书。太逊了！
-We do Audible here. We do that. Does that count?
我们这里听 Audible，这算吗？
-I think it's time for you to get me back.
我觉得现在轮到你反击我了。
-Okay, so – It's based on this book.
好的，所以——它是根据这本书改编的。
-Yeah. No, too late. No, too late.
是啊。不了，太晚了，太晚了。
-But this is based on the big best-selling book.
但这部电影是根据一本非常畅销的书改编的。
-Well, the book does have a fan following somewhere.
这本书确实在某些地方拥有自己的粉丝群。
-And I think the book is incredible.
我觉得这本书非常棒。
-And Hayes Campbell is so beautifully written in the book.
书里的 Hayes Campbell 这个角色塑造得非常精彩。
-And so we knew that we just really needed to find someone really special.
所以我们知道，我们真的需要找到一个非常特别的人来出演。
-And he walked in, yeah, and I just thought, "Oh, that's Hayes Campbell."
然后他走进来，我当时就想："哦，这就是 Hayes Campbell。"
-And that was almost two years ago.
那已经是将近两年前的事情了。
-And now Nick and I have become really good friends, and, yeah, it's opened up in this beautiful way.
现在 Nick 和我已经成为非常好的朋友，而且这段关系以一种很美好的方式发展起来。
-Hi again.
嗨，又见面了。
-Are you a part of that ASMR community that gets off on listening to people pee?
你是不是那个 ASMR 社群的一员？他们喜欢听别人小便的声音来获得刺激？
-No, I wasn't -Because I don't think you can just go around assuming –
-不，我不是。 -因为我觉得你不能随便到处假设……
-It's actually my trailer.
其实这是我的休息车。
-It's not literally mine. You know, I don't own it.
它并不是字面意义上属于我的。你知道，我并不拥有它。
-This is your trailer?
这是你的休息车？
-Yeah, I'm in the band. We're performing on the main stage.
对，我是乐队成员。我们会在主舞台表演。
-You know, I'm Hayes Campbell. -August Moon? -Yeah.
-你知道，我就是 Hayes Campbell。-August Moon? -对。
-Well, I absolutely know who you are.
当然，我非常清楚你是谁。
-Anyway… I'll…
不管怎样，我……
-Yeah. Come on. You know how to do it.
来吧，你知道该怎么做。
-Anne Hathaway, everybody. Anne Hathaway，
各位。
-"The Idea of You" begins streaming on Prime Video this Thursday. 《The Idea of You》
《The Idea of You》本周四开始在 Prime Video 上线播放。
-We'll be right back with Melanie Lynskey.
稍后我们会继续邀请 Melanie Lynskey 回到节目。
-Stick around, everybody.
大家不要走开。